American Federation of Labor Records, Part 2 on Microfilm 5760 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Convention File, 1935-1952 (Reel 13)
  - 0002. Box 16/Folder 2. Organizing Campaign - State Federations Conference. 99 pages., 1949-1950; 2 (Reel 13)
  - 0101. Box 16/Folder 2. Organizing Campaign - 1950. 36 pages., 1949-1950; 3 (Reel 13)
  - 0137. Box 16/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1949-1950; 4 (Reel 13)
  - 0138. Box 16/Folder 3. Political Candidates. 2 pages., 1949; 5 (Reel 13)
  - 0140. Box 16/Folder 3. President's Safety Conference. 6 pages., 1949; 6 (Reel 13)
  - 0146. Box 16/Folder 3. Public Relations - Radio and Labor Press. 18 pages., 1949-1950; 7 (Reel 13)
  - 0164. Box 16/Folder 3. Puerto Rico. 9 pages., 1950; 8 (Reel 13)
  - 0173. Box 16/Folder 3. Puerto Rico - Labor Conditions. 42 pages., 1949-1950; 9 (Reel 13)
  - 0215. Box 16/Folder 3. Resolutions - Record of Reference to Departments for Attention. 18 pages., 1949-1950; 10 (Reel 13)
  - 0233. Box 16/Folder 3. Reports - Publications, Departments, and Committees. 38 pages., 1949; 11 (Reel 13)
  - 0271. Box 16/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1949-1950; 12 (Reel 13)
  - 0272. Box 16/Folder 4. Seafarers - Merchant Marine. 4 pages., 1949; 13 (Reel 13)
  - 0276. Box 16/Folder 4. Shorter Workweek. 2 pages., 1949; 14 (Reel 13)
  - 0278. Box 16/Folder 4. Strike Benefits. 3 pages., 1949; 15 (Reel 13)
  - 0281. Box 16/Folder 4. Taft-Hartley Act. 9 pages., 1950; 16 (Reel 13)
  - 0290. Box 16/Folder 4. United Nations - United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization (UNESCO). 84 pages., 1949-1950; 17 (Reel 13)
  - 0374. Box 16/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1949-1950; 18 (Reel 13)
  - 0375. Box 16/Folder 5. Union Label Week. 9 pages., 1949-1950; 19 (Reel 13)
  - 0384. Box 16/Folder 5. White Collar Workers. 3 pages., 1949-1950; 20 (Reel 13)
  - 0387. Box 16/Folder 5. Workers Education Bureau. 40 pages., 1949-1950; 21 (Reel 13)
  - 0427. Box 16/Folder 5. Resolutions - No Action Necessary and Non-Concurred. 11 pages., 1949; 22 (Reel 13)
  - 0438. Box 17/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1950-1951; 23 (Reel 13)
  - 0439. Box 17/Folder 1. Africa and the Point Four Program. 2 pages., 1950; 24 (Reel 13)
  - 0441. Box 17/Folder 1. African Federation. 2 pages., 1950; 25 (Reel 13)
  - 0443. Box 17/Folder 1. American Commercial Fleet. 29 pages., 1950-1951; 26 (Reel 13)
  - 0472. Box 17/Folder 1. Boycott- Products of Slave Labor. 8 pages., 1950-1951; 27 (Reel 13)
  - 0480. Box 17/Folder 1. C.A.R.E. 7 pages., 1950; 28 (Reel 13)
  - 0487. Box 17/Folder 1. Civil Rights. 2 pages., 1950; 29 (Reel 13)
  - 0489. Box 17/Folder 1. Communism. 15 pages., 1950; 30 (Reel 13)
  - 0504. Box 17/Folder 1. Convention - Hotel Accommodations. 5 pages., 1950; 31 (Reel 13)
  - 0509. Box 17/Folder 1. Declaration of Human Rights. 5 pages., 1950; 32 (Reel 13)
  - 0514. Box 17/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention. Economic Cooperation Administration (ECA). 267 pages., 1950-1951; 33 (Reel 13)
  - 0781. Box 17/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1950-1951; 34 (Reel 13)
  - 0782. Box 17/Folder 3. Education in European Communities - Financing. 2 pages., 1950; 35 (Reel 13)
  - 0784. Box 17/Folder 3. Election Day Holiday. 4 pages., 1950; 36 (Reel 13)
  - 0788. Box 17/Folder 3. Enlisted Personnel - Navy Shipyards. 9 pages., 1950-1951; 37 (Reel 13)
  - 0797. Box 17/Folder 3. Expose Stockholm Petition. 6 pages., 1950; 38 (Reel 13)
  - 0803. Box 17/Folder 3. Farm Subsidies. 5 pages., 1950; 39 (Reel 13)
  - 0808. Box 17/Folder 3. Farm Workers - Collective Bargaining Rights. 6 pages., 1950-1951; 40 (Reel 13)
  - 0814. Box 17/Folder 3. Firefighters - Wages and Working Conditions. 11 pages., 1950-1951; 41 (Reel 13)
  - 0825/ Box 17/Folder 3. Flag Day - Observance. 2 pages., 1950; 42 (Reel 13)
  - 0827. Box 17/Folder 3. Fraternal Delegates. 70 pages., 1950; 43 (Reel 13)
  - 0897. Box 17/Folder 3. Free Trade Union Committee. 6 pages., 44 (Reel 13)
  - 0903. Box 17/Folder 3. German Property - Return to Former Owners. 2 pages., 1950; 45 (Reel 13)
  - 0905. Box 17/Folder 3. Gompers Centenary - Report. 36 pages., 1950-1951; 46 (Reel 13)
  - 0941. Box 17/Folder 3. Gompers Institute of Labor Relations. 2 pages., 1950; 47 (Reel 13)
  - 0943. Box 17/Folder 3. Guantanamo Naval Base - Employee Wages. 7 pages., 1950; 48 (Reel 13)
  - 0950. Box 17/Folder 3. Hawaii - Aid for American Federation of Labor (AFL) Unions. 9 pages., 1950-1951; 49 (Reel 13)
- Convention File, 1935-1952 (Reel 14)
  - 0001. Box 17/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1950-1951; 1 (Reel 14)
  - 0002. Box 17/Folder 4. International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU) - Milan Congress of July 1951. 79 pages., 2 (Reel 14)
  - 0080. Box 17/Folder 4. International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU) - Executive Board and General. 109 pages., 1950-1951; 3 (Reel 14)
  - 0189. Box 17/Folder 4. International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU) - Board Meeting, Milan. July 1951. 122 pages., 4 (Reel 14)
  - 0311. Box 18/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1950-1951; 5 (Reel 14)
  - 0312. Box 18/Folder 1. International Labor Relations - China. 32 pages., 1950-1951; 6 (Reel 14)
  - 0344. Box 18/Folder 1. International Labor Relations - Germany/Austria. 81 pages., 1950-1951; 7 (Reel 14)
  - 0425. Box 18/Folder 1. International Labor Relations - India. 23 pages., 1950-1951; 8 (Reel 14)
  - 0428. Box 18/Folder 1. International Labor Relations - Italy. 44 pages., 1950-1951; 9 (Reel 14)
  - 0472. Box 18/Folder 1. International Labor Relations - Japan. 30 pages., 1950-1951; 10 (Reel 14)
  - 0502. Box 18/Folder 1. International Labor Relations - Korea (ROK). 12 pages., 1951; 11 (Reel 14)
  - 0514. Box 18/Folder 1. International Labor Relations - Spain. 35 pages., 1951; 12 (Reel 14)
  - 0549. Box 18/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention. International Labor Organization. 147 pages., 1950-1951; 13 (Reel 14)
  - 0696. Box 18/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention. International Labor Relations - Miscellaneous. 177 pages., 1950-1951; 14 (Reel 14)
  - 0873. Box 18/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention. International Longshoremen's Association - New York State Crime Commission Report. 164 pages., 1953; 15 (Reel 14)
- Convention File, 1935-1952 (Reel 15)
  - 0001. Box 19/Folder 1. Correspondence and papers relating to Convention., 1949-1951; 1 (Reel 15)
  - 0002. Box 19/Folder 1. Ireland. 6 pages., 1950; 2 (Reel 15)
  - 0008. Box 19/Folder 1. Jewish Labor Committee. 2 pages., 1950; 3 (Reel 15)
  - 0010. Box 19/Folder 1. Korea (ROK). 9 pages., 1950-1951; 4 (Reel 15)
  - 0019. Box 19/Folder 1. Labor Representation in Foreign Policy. 14 pages., 1950-1951; 5 (Reel 15)
  - 0033. Box 19/Folder 1. Labor Unity. 2 pages., 1950; 6 (Reel 15)
  - 0035. Box 19/Folder 1. Machinists - Reafilliation. 86 pages., 1950-1951; 7 (Reel 15)
  - 0121. Box 19/Folder 1. Mexico, American Actors in. 6 pages., 1950; 8 (Reel 15)
  - 0127. Box 19/Folder 1. Military Encroachment - Civilian occupations. 4 pages., 1950-1951; 9 (Reel 15)
  - 0131. Box 19/Folder 1. National Labor Relations Board - Counsel Denham Removed. 6 pages., 1950; 10 (Reel 15)
  - 0137. Box 19/Folder 1. Official Changes. 19 pages., 1949-1950; 11 (Reel 15)
  - 0156. Box 19/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1950-1951; 12 (Reel 15)
  - 0157. Box 19/Folder 2. Organizing Activities. 70 pages., 1950-1951; 13 (Reel 15)
  - 0227. Box 19/Folder 2. Pension Plans. 9 pages., 1950; 14 (Reel 15)
  - 0236. Box 19/Folder 2. Program to Reach Russian People. 8 pages., 1950-1951; 15 (Reel 15)
  - 0244. Box 19/Folder 2. Promulgate our Democratic Creed. 8 pages., 1950-1951; 16 (Reel 15)
  - 0252. Box 19/Folder 2. Public Relations - Radio and the Labor Press. 17 pages., 1950; 17 (Reel 15)
  - 0269. Box 19/Folder 2. American Federation of Labor Radio Broadcasts. 5 pages., 1950; 18 (Reel 15)
  - 0274. Box 19/Folder 2. Auditing and Credentials Committee. 12 pages., 1950; 19 (Reel 15)
  - 0286. Box 19/Folder 2. Resolutions - Record of Reference to Department for Attention. 13 pages., 1950; 20 (Reel 15)
  - 0299. Box 19/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers Relating to Convention., 1950-1951; 21 (Reel 15)
  - 0300. Box 19/Folder 3. Reports - Executive Council, Office of Legal Counsel, and Departments. 144 pages., 1950-1951; 22 (Reel 15)
  - 0444. Box 19/Folder 3. School for International Affairs. 8 pages., 1950-1951; 23 (Reel 15)
  - 0452. Box 19/Folder 3. Southern Organizing Campaign. 2 pages., 1950; 24 (Reel 15)
  - 0454. Box 19/Folder 3. State and Central Body Affiliation. 3 pages., 1950; 25 (Reel 15)
  - 0457. Box 19/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1950-1951; 26 (Reel 15)
  - 0458. Box 19/Folder 4. Stitzel-Weller Company - Anti-Union Activities. 2 pages., 1950; 27 (Reel 15)
  - 0460. Box 19/Folder 4. Strike Benefits. 6 pages., 1950-1951; 28 (Reel 15)
  - 0466. Box 19/Folder 4. Trade Union Advisory Committee - Department of Labor.; 5 pages., 1950-1951; 29 (Reel 15)
  - 0471. Box 19/Folder 4. United Nations Education, Scientific, and Cultural Organization (UNESCO). 21 pages., 1950-1951; 30 (Reel 15)
  - 0492. Box 19/Folder 4. Union Label. 7 pages., 1950; 31 (Reel 15)
  - 0499. Box 19/Folder 4. Union Labor Veterans - National Conference. 2 pages., 1950; 32 (Reel 15)
  - 0501. Box 19/Folder 4. United Mine Workers. 3 pages., 1950; 33 (Reel 15)
  - 0504. Box 19/Folder 4. United Nations. 16 pages., 1950-1951; 34 (Reel 15)
  - 0520. Box 19/Folder 4. Wage Rates In Puerto Rico. 7 pages., 1950; 35 (Reel 15)
  - 0527. Box 19/Folder 4. Wages and Prices. 17 pages., 1950-1951; 36 (Reel 15)
  - 0544. Box 19/Folder 4. Workers Education Bureau. 28 pages., 1950-1951; 37 (Reel 15)
  - 0572. Box 19/Folder 4. Resolutions - No Action Necessary and Non-Concurred. 11 pages., 1950; 38 (Reel 15)
  - 0583. Box 20/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1951-1952; 39 (Reel 15)
  - 0584. Box 20/Folder 1. Anchorage, Alaska - Freight Rates. 8 pages., 1951; 40 (Reel 15)
  - 0592. Box 20/Folder 1. Boilermakers-Blacksmiths Amalgamation. 12 pages., 1951; 41 (Reel 15)
  - 0602. Box 20/Folder 1. Bond Program, United States Savings. 7 pages., 1951-1952; 42 (Reel 15)
  - 0609. Box 20/Folder 1. C.A.R.E. 4 pages., 1951; 43 (Reel 15)
  - 0614. Box 20/Folder 1. Civil Rates, American Federation of Labor work on. 3 pages., 1951; 44 (Reel 15)
  - 0617. Box 20/Folder 1. Communism - Economic Trends in Europe and the Middle East. 63 pages., 1951-1952; 45 (Reel 15)
  - 0680. Box 20/Folder 1. Community Chests and Councils. 6 pages., 1951; 46 (Reel 15)
  - 0686. Box 20/Folder 1. Conversion of Defense Plant Facilities. 6 pages., 1951-1952; 47 (Reel 15)
  - 0692. Box 20/Folder 1. Daily Labor Press. 4 pages., 1951-1952; 48 (Reel 15)
  - 0696. Box 20/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1951-1952; 49 (Reel 15)
  - 0697. Box 20/Folder 2. Defense Orders - Union Shops. 10 pages., 1951; 50 (Reel 15)
  - 0707. Box 20/Folder 2. Farm Organizations. 26 pages., 1951; 51 (Reel 15)
  - 0733. Box 20/Folder 2. Federal Labor Union Conferences. 3 pages., 1951; 52 (Reel 15)
  - 0736. Box 20/Folder 2. Free Trade Union Committee. 25 pages., 1951-1952; 53 (Reel 15)
  - 0761. Box 20/Folder 2. Histadrut-Israeli Federation of Labor. 2 pages., 1951; 54 (Reel 15)
  - 0763. Box 20/Folder 2. Housing - Advisory Committee Home Finance Agency. 15 pages., 1951; 55 (Reel 15)
  - 0778. Box 20/Folder 2. Insurance Agents Strike - Prudential Insurance Company. 39 pages., 1951-1952; 56 (Reel 15)
  - 0817. Box 20/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU). 182 pages., 1950- 1952; 57 (Reel 15)
- Convention File, 1935-1952 (Reel 16)
  - 0001. Box 20/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU). 235 pages., 1952; 1 (Reel 16)
    January-June 1952.
  - 0236. Box 20/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1952; 2 (Reel 16)
  - 0237. Box 20/Folder 5. International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU). 139 pages., 1952; 3 (Reel 16)
    June-December, 1952.
  - 0376. Box 20/Folder 5. Replies to Letter of May 2 regarding International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU). 50 pages., 1952; 4 (Reel 16)
  - 0426. Box 21/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - International Labour Organization. 138 pages., 1950-1952; 5 (Reel 16)
    1950-January 1952.
  - 0565. Box 21/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - International Labour Organization. 144 pages., 1952; 6 (Reel 16)
    January- September, 1952
  - 0710. Box 21/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1950-1952; 7 (Reel 16)
  - 0711. Box 21/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - General Matters. 60 pages., 1950-1952; 8 (Reel 16)
  - 0771. Box 21/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Albania. 5 pages., 1952; 9 (Reel 16)
  - 0776. Box 21/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Australia. 3 pages., 1952; 10 (Reel 16)
  - 0779. Box 21/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - China (ROC). 6 pages., 1951-1952; 11 (Reel 16)
  - 0785. Box 21/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Denmark. 12 pages., 1952; 12 (Reel 16)
  - 0797. Box 21/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - France. 10 pages., 1951-1952; 13 (Reel 16)
  - 0807. Box 21/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Germany/Austria. 129 pages., 1950-1952; 14 (Reel 16)
  - 0936. Box 21/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - Greece. 5 pages., 1952; 15 (Reel 16)
  - 0941. Box 21/Folder 3. International Labor Relations - India. 32 pages., 1951-1952; 16 (Reel 16)
- Convention File, 1935-1952 (Reel 17)
  - 0001. Box 21/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1951-1952; 1 (Reel 17)
  - 0002. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Indonesia. 15 pages., 1951-1952; 2 (Reel 17)
  - 0017. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Israel. 5 pages., 1951; 3 (Reel 17)
  - 0022. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Italy. 23 pages., 1951-1952; 4 (Reel 17)
  - 0045. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Japan. 97 pages., 1951-1952; 5 (Reel 17)
  - 0142. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Korea (ROK). 13 pages., 1951-1952; 6 (Reel 17)
  - 0155. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Latin America. 26 pages., 1951-1952; 7 (Reel 17)
  - 0181. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Morocco. 15 pages., 1952; 8 (Reel 17)
  - 0196. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Pakistan. 10 pages., 1952; 9 (Reel 17)
  - 0206. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Poland. 14 pages., 1952; 10 (Reel 17)
  - 0220. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - South Africa. 7 pages., 1952; 11 (Reel 17)
  - 0227. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Spain. 9 pages., 1952; 12 (Reel 17)
  - 0236. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Switzerland. 6 pages., 1952; 13 (Reel 17)
  - 0242. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Tunisia. 29 pages., 1952; 14 (Reel 17)
  - 0271. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Turkey. 6 pages., 1951-1952; 15 (Reel 17)
  - 0277. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Turks Island. 7 pages., 1951; 16 (Reel 17)
  - 0284. Box 21/Folder 4. International Labor Relations - Yugoslavia. 5 pages., 1951; 17 (Reel 17)
  - 0289. Box 21/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1950-1952; 18 (Reel 17)
  - 0290. Box 21/Folder 5. Partition of Ireland. 11 pages., 1951; 19 (Reel 17)
  - 0301. Box 21/Folder 5. Italian Peace Treaty. 10 pages., 1951; 20 (Reel 17)
  - 0311. Box 21/Folder 5. Labor Press Committee. 9 pages., 1951-1952; 21 (Reel 17)
  - 0320. Box 21/Folder 5. Machinists - Reafilliation. 61 pages., 1950-1951; 22 (Reel 17)
  - 0381. Box 21/Folder 5. Meat Cutters-Leather Workers Amalgamation. 22 pages., 1951; 23 (Reel 17)
  - 0403. Box 21/Folder 5. Mexican-United States Labor Cooperation. 63 pages., 1951-1952; 24 (Reel 17)
  - 0466. Box 22/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention - Mutual Security Administration (North Atlantic Treaty Organization and ECA). 199 pages., 1951-1952; 25 (Reel 17)
  - 0665. Box 22/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1951-1952; 26 (Reel 17)
  - 0666. Box 22/Folder 2. Organization - Atomic Energy Plants. 5 pages., 1951; 27 (Reel 17)
  - 0671. Box 22/Folder 2. Organization - Expansion of American Federation of Labor Program. 6 pages., 1951; 28 (Reel 17)
  - 0677. Box 22/Folder 2. Organization - Southern California Campaign. 52 pages., 1951-1952; 29 (Reel 17)
  - 0729. Box 22/Folder 2. Printing Paper - Cost and Shortage. 3 pages., 1951; 30 (Reel 17)
  - 0732. Box 22/Folder 2. Sugar - Sturdy of Domestic Situation. 4 pages., 1951; 31 (Reel 17)
  - 0736. Box 22/Folder 2. Taft-Hartley Act. 15 pages., 1951; 32 (Reel 17)
  - 0751. Box 22/Folder 2. Tobacco Workers-Teamsters Jurisdictional Dispute. 13 pages., 1951-1952; 33 (Reel 17)
  - 0764. Box 22/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1951-1952; 34 (Reel 17)
  - 0765. Box 22/Folder 3. United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization. 32 pages., 1951-1952; 35 (Reel 17)
  - 0797. Box 22/Folder 3. Union Label. 5 pages., 1951; 36 (Reel 17)
  - 0802. Box 22/Folder 3. United Labor Policy Committee. 13 pages., 1951; 37 (Reel 17)
  - 0815. Box 22/Folder 3. United Nations. 36 pages., 1951-1952; 38 (Reel 17)
  - 0851. Box 22/Folder 3. Unity - AFL-CIO Conferences. 14 pages., 1951-1952; 39 (Reel 17)
  - 0865. Box 22/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1951-1952; 40 (Reel 17)
  - 0866. Box 22/Folder 4. Wage Stabilization. 101 pages., 1951; 41 (Reel 17)
  - 0967. Box 22/Folder 4. Women Workers. 7 pages., 1951; 42 (Reel 17)
  - 0974. Box 22/Folder 4. Wage Stabilization. 83 pages., 1952; 43 (Reel 17)
- Convention File, 1935-1952 Relations with the Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1935-1950. (Reel 18)
  - 0001. Box 23/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1952-1953; 1 (Reel 18)
  - 0002. Box 23/Folder 1. American Book Company - Anti-Union Activities. 7 pages., 1952; 2 (Reel 18)
  - 0009. Box 23/Folder 1. American Federationist. 4 pages., 1952; 3 (Reel 18)
  - 0013. Box 23/Folder 1. Appeal - C.A.R.E. 8 pages., 1952; 4 (Reel 18)
  - 0021. Box 23/Folder 1. Civil Defense. 7 pages., 1952; 5 (Reel 18)
  - 0028. Box 23/Folder 1. Community Chests - Defense Funds. 9 pages., 1952-1953; 6 (Reel 18)
  - 0037. Box 23/Folder 1. Curtis Publishing Company, Organization of. 7 pages., 1952; 7 (Reel 18)
  - 0044. Box 23/Folder 1. Firefighters-Operating Engineers Jurisdictional Dispute. 26 pages., 1952-1953; 8 (Reel 18)
  - 0070. Box 23/Folder 1. Foreign-Made Motion Pictures. 7 pages., 1952; 9 (Reel 18)
  - 0077. Box 23/Folder 1. Free Trade Union Committee. 5 pages., 1952; 10 (Reel 18)
  - 0082. Box 23/Folder 1. Gompers Memorial - City of Hope, California. 42 pages., 1952; 11 (Reel 18)
  - 0106. Box 23/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1952-1953; 12 (Reel 18)
  - 0107. Box 23/Folder 2. Government Printing Office - Minimum Pay for Bookbinders. 12 pages., 1952; 13 (Reel 18)
  - 0119. Box 23/Folder 2. Health Protection Services. 7 pages., 1952; 14 (Reel 18)
  - 0126. Box 23/Folder 2. Histadrut. 10 pages., 1952; 15 (Reel 18)
  - 0136. Box 23/Folder 2. Insurance Companies - Organizing Campaign. 9 pages., 1952; 16 (Reel 18)
  - 0145. Box 23/Folder 2. International Labor Organization. 47 pages., 1952-1953; 17 (Reel 18)
  - 0192. Box 23/Folder 2. International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU). 45 pages., 1952-1953; 18 (Reel 18)
  - 0237. Box 23/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1952-1953; 19 (Reel 18)
  - 0238. Box 23/Folder 3. Italy, Boys' Town of. 7 pages., 1952; 20 (Reel 18)
  - 0245. Box 23/Folder 3. Jurisdictional Disputes between American Federation of Labor Unions. 7 pages., 1952; 21 (Reel 18)
  - 0252. Box 23/Folder 3. Justice Department - Ruling on Motion Pictures. 15 pages., 1952-1953; 22 (Reel 18)
  - 0267. Box 23/Folder 3. Labor's Daily - ITU. 5 pages., 1952; 23 (Reel 18)
  - 0272. Box 23/Folder 3. Labor Unity. 17 pages., 1952; 24 (Reel 18)
  - 0289. Box 23/Folder 3. Latin America. 17 pages., 1952; 25 (Reel 18)
  - 0306. Box 23/Folder 3. Legislation (State), Department of. 8 pages., 1952-1953; 26 (Reel 18)
  - 0314. Box 23/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1952; 27 (Reel 18)
  - 0315. Box 23/Folder 4. Mutual Security Agency - ECA. 13 pages., 1952; 28 (Reel 18)
  - 0328. Box 23/Folder 4. Senator McMahon - Nobel Peace Prize Requested. 8 pages., 1952; 29 (Reel 18)
  - 0336. Box 23/Folder 4. Postmaster General, Orders of the. 5 pages., 1952; 30 (Reel 18)
  - 0341. Box 23/Folder 4. Political Matters. 106 pages., 1952; 31 (Reel 18)
  - 0447. Box 23/Folder 5. Correspondence and Papers relating to Convention., 1952-1953; 32 (Reel 18)
  - 0448. Box 23/Folder 5. Organization - Craft Union. 13 pages., 1952-1953; 33 (Reel 18)
  - 0461. Box 23/Folder 5. Resolutions Committee - Recommendations. 15 pages., 1952; 34 (Reel 18)
  - 0486. Box 23/Folder 5. State and City Central Body - Local Union Affiliation. 9 pages., 1952; 35 (Reel 18)
  - 0494. Box 23/Folder 5. Taft-Hartley Act, Developments under the. 44 pages., 1952; 36 (Reel 18)
  - 0538. Box 23/Folder 5. TV Channels for Labor Educational Programs. 6 pages., 1952-1953; 37 (Reel 18)
  - 0544. Box 23/Folder 5. Union Label - Clubs. 7 pages., 1952; 38 (Reel 18)
  - 0551. Box 23/Folder 5. Union Label - Councils. 7 pages., 1952; 39 (Reel 18)
  - 0558. Box 23/Folder 5. Union Industries Show - Participation Urged. 7 pages., 1952; 40 (Reel 18)
  - 0565. United Nations - United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization. 13 pages., 1952; 41 (Reel 18)
  - 0578. Box 23/Folder 5. Women Workers. 3 pages., 1952; 42 (Reel 18)
  - 0581. Box 24/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations., 1935-1937; 43 (Reel 18)
  - 0582. Box 24/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 7 pages., 1935; 44 (Reel 18)
  - 0589. Box 24/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 85 pages., 1936; 45 (Reel 18)
  - 0674. Box 24/Folder 1. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 161 pages., 1937; 46 (Reel 18)
  - 0835. Box 24/Folder 2. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 260 pages., 1937-1938; 47 (Reel 18)
    October 1937-January 1938.
- Relations with the Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1935-1950 (Reel 19)
  - Box 24/Folder 3. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 202 pages., 1938; 1 (Reel 19)
    January-September 1938
  - 0203. Box 24/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations., 1938-1942; 2 (Reel 19)
  - 0204. Box 24/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 32 pages., 1938; 3 (Reel 19)
    October-December 1938.
  - 0236. Box 24/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 103 pages., 1939; 4 (Reel 19)
    January- December 1939
  - 0339. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 30 pages., 1940; 5 (Reel 19)
    January-June 1940.
  - 0369. Box 24/Folder 4. Correspondence and Papers relating to the Congress of Industrial Organizations. 18 pages., 1941; 6 (Reel 19)
    September- December 1941.